<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Where is Xinlu]]></title><description><![CDATA[Where is Xinlu]]></description><link>http://xinluh.github.io/where-am-i</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 05:14:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Utah Highway 12 and Zebra Slot Canyon]]></title><description><![CDATA[It was a nice respite from the gloom and doom to drive on Utah Highway 12 from Torrey to Bryce, through winter wonderland of snow-covered…]]></description><link>http://xinluh.github.io/where-am-i/utah-highway-12-and-zebra-slot-canyon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://xinluh.github.io/where-am-i/utah-highway-12-and-zebra-slot-canyon/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 04:12:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;It was a nice respite from the gloom and doom to drive on Utah Highway 12 from Torrey to Bryce, through winter wonderland of snow-covered aspen groves dotting pristine snow fields near the mountain top, and through the incredibly colorful and expansive rocky landscape of Grand Staircase-Escalante National Monument.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We stopped for a hike to the Zebra Slot Canyon, just north of Escalate off the unpaved Hole-in-the-Rock road. I was a bit concerned about the unpaved road condition after the rain yesterday, but it turned out okay. We had just a tantalizing glimpse of the “Zebra” part of the slot canyon - the water level in the slot canyon was high, and we turned back about 50 ft beyond the canyon entrance, after wading through above-waist-high cold muddy water. Would love to come back and explore further, when the water level gets low enough so swimming is not required!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Travel in the Time of Coronavirus]]></title><description><![CDATA[I started planning the logistics of this trip in early Jan before coronavirus / COVID-19 entered the news; in early Feb, I chose the…]]></description><link>http://xinluh.github.io/where-am-i/travel-in-the-time-of-coronavirus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://xinluh.github.io/where-am-i/travel-in-the-time-of-coronavirus/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 05:29:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I started planning the logistics of this trip in early Jan before coronavirus / COVID-19 entered the news; in early Feb, I chose the departure date (eventually pushed back by 1 week) at the time when daily new cases number in the US was 0 or in the low single digits; I started driving on March 6, just a few days after the first death in the US was announced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As of today, 1 week into my trip, the US is in a state of emergency with mass closures of everything from schools to Broadway. The ski resort where I’ve been skiing this week is now closed (a quick turn of event - just this morning, Vail Resorts sent an email stating that resorts would in fact stay open, but with reduced operations and encouragement of social distancing). Depending on how obsessively one follows the news, it seems like the world is spiraling into panic mode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All that is to say, the situation took a drastic turn for the worse in a very short time. I thought I was mentally prepared for the power of exponential growth, but the reactions by ordinary people, organizations, governments, etc. still took me by surprise. With foresight I would certainly choose a different time to do some long term travelling, but no point in wondering about “what could have happened if I have known…” - unexpected hairpin turns are part of why life is so interesting anyways!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, the US is vast and barely inhabited outside of the coasts. Road trip with long stretches of driving are effectively self-quarantine. I’ll make the best of the situation by being flexible - for once, time is on my side. Hopefully the backcountry of the national parks remains accessible…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Onward!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hello World]]></title><description><![CDATA[I might write something here from time to time.]]></description><link>http://xinluh.github.io/where-am-i/hello-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://xinluh.github.io/where-am-i/hello-world/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I might write something here from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>